<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Xaver Fuchs Research</title>
    <link>https://xaverfuchs.github.io/xaverfuchsde/docs/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Xaver Fuchs Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xaverfuchs.github.io/xaverfuchsde/docs/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Modding the Zoom B1Four Bass Multieffect Processor</title>
      <link>https://xaverfuchs.github.io/xaverfuchsde/docs/post/2022/10/02/modding-zoom-b1four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xaverfuchs.github.io/xaverfuchsde/docs/post/2022/10/02/modding-zoom-b1four/</guid>
      <description>The Zoom B1Four The Zoom B1Four is a fantastic low budget multieffect processor for electric bass. It is packed with features like effects, amp simulations and even a looper and a drum machine. Sounds can be easily edited using a software when the pedal is connected to the computer using a USB cable. The device costs just something like 90 Euros.
This is how it looks like.
There is one downside to the Zoom though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle Animations</title>
      <link>https://xaverfuchs.github.io/xaverfuchsde/docs/post/2022/02/20/circleanimations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xaverfuchs.github.io/xaverfuchsde/docs/post/2022/02/20/circleanimations/</guid>
      <description>Floating circles animation This is a svg-based animation that uses randomness. Circles have a random starting point when loading the page and then move in a random-walk fashion across the screen.
  //Script to randomize starting attributes function getRandomInt(min, max) { return Math.floor(Math.random() * (max - min + 1) + min); } function getRandColor(brightness){ // Six levels of brightness from 0 to 5, 0 being the darkest var rgb = [Math.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Square Animations</title>
      <link>https://xaverfuchs.github.io/xaverfuchsde/docs/post/2022/02/02/squareanimations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xaverfuchs.github.io/xaverfuchsde/docs/post/2022/02/02/squareanimations/</guid>
      <description>Square-shaped animations About these animations I created these animations using the R programming language. The animations are based on randomness. Random walks were used to create unpredictable changes in colors or of objects moving on the canvas. In some animations, I combined the R-created footage with pictures or movies that I found on the internet or recorded with my mobile phone. I started making these animations during my PhD, probably around 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
